got a message today about Joe. At the
very end of it, it said, "Your pursuit
of knowledge has inspired the pursuit in
many. Let their light carry the mission
while you rekindle your flame." Boy,
y'all better be carrying some solar
flare type flashlights. I'm healing, not
healed. There's a big difference between
the two. And since we've been back from
Costa Rica the last 2 months, life has
made damn sure I understood that. It
reminded me of something I've heard that
I think Joe has smacked down in the
middle of learning.
We have to stop cursing the season that
we are currently in that is meant to
create capacity inside of us. I'm guilty
of it. Joe's hella guilty of it. Why me?
Why now? Those problems are not there to
completely destroy us. [music] They are
there to develop us. Whatever higher
power you believe in
>> [music]
>> is not going to remove your problems
until you become the person capable of
handling what's after them. If
>> [music]
>> your circumstances change before your
character does, you're just going to
create the same prison. You have not
evolved. You've done nothing. You quit.
You gave up. Here you go. Back to square
one. Example, this one's good for Joe.
You prayed for freedom, right, before
you learned responsibility. If you have
yet to learn that responsibility, that
freedom doesn't become an opportunity.
That freedom becomes a world for you to
self-destruct [music]
in. We as humans have mastered the art
of asking
somebody to fix it. We've [music]
forgotten how to ask to fix us so that
then we can fix it. [music] If you can't
handle too much when it's a struggle,
what makes you think you'll be able to
handle it when it's a success? I say it
all the time. You got to go through hell
to get to heaven. And life is a roller
coaster, man. And And it's never going
to stop. This, up and down, up and down.
But this, the dip, this is not
punishment. This is
preparation for the next client. And And
if you can't
get through this, you're not finna get
up here.
For us surely right now this is a season
of change. This is a season of growth.
This is a season of uncertainty. This is
a season of [__] But it's it's
healthy [__] Life has done a
complete 180 in the last 2 months.
[music] But I know that we're going to
be okay. I don't know what the future
holds for Joe Fells, but I do know one
thing and that is Joe Fells holds his
future.
And so do you. Nobody's coming to fix
this for you. Stop asking for an easier
path and just become a stronger person.
That's the game. It's the whole purpose.
Trust your feet.